## PROFILE

I'm a Technical Support Superhero and QA Apprentice at ONTRAPORT, a rapidly-growing Business and Marketing Automation software company in Santa Barbara. I've found that customers and software developers often have divergent definitions of what constitutes a Bug. I take the opportunity to be the "People's Champion" and don't settle for resolutions that are less than ideal for our customers. Through my experience at ONTRAPORT, I've found a bit of a niche — translating between the technical and nontechnical.



# Kevin Eales Monroe

**Technical Support Wizard** 

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Quality Assurance Apprentice**

ONTRAPORT - Santa Barbara, CA

Jan 2017 - Present

Internal internship in our QA Engineering department concurrent with Superhero position

- Provide deeper troubleshooting on tickets escalated from Technical Support
- Assign priority on bug tickets and dispatch JIRA tickets to development team
- Verify resolution of tickets before code is deployed to production
- · Follow up with clients through Zendesk once bug tickets are resolved

#### **Technical Support Superhero**

Sept 2016 - Present

ONTRAPORT - Santa Barbara, CA

- · Troubleshoot and answer tickets escalated from Level 1 support
- Provide support for our API, integrations, and other advanced features
- Determine if a bug is systemwide and perform appropriate testing
- · Develop internal training documentation
- Mentor Level 1 representatives and provide peer leadership

### **Customer Support Hero**

Jan 2016 - Sept 2016

ONTRAPORT - Santa Barbara, CA

- Provided exceptional frontline support to our customers via phone, chat, and email
- Fielded on average 160 tickets per week
- Communicated clearly and effectively on how complex features work
- Provided triage for issues coming in, troubleshooting issues quickly and efficiently
- Led the team 2016 stats in both satisfaction (97%) and tickets solved (4,700)

#### **IT Administrator Intern**

July 2014 - April 2015

Graphiq (formerly FindTheBest) - Santa Barbara, CA

- Provided helpdesk support for both Windows and OS X
- Administrated G Suite among other SaaS apps
- · Maintained and built out network infrastructure as needed to accommodate growth
- Purchased and provisioned IT equipment and SaaS accounts for all new employees

#### Network Administrator Intern

Oct 2013 - July 2014

Marvin Test Solutions - Irvine, CA

- · Provided helpdesk support on an all-Windows network
- · Administrated Active Domain, MS Exchange, and keycards
- Spearheaded project to upgrade remaining XP workstations to Win7 before XP's end-of-life
- Upgraded Exchange, SQL, and file server from Windows Server 2003 to Server 2012

kevin [at] eales [dot] co (mailto: kevin@eales.co)

**&** 805 698 7435 (tel:18056987325)

eales.co (http://eales.co)

in linkedin.com/in/kealesmonroe
(https://www.linkedin.com/in/kealesmonroe/)

#### **EDUCATION**

Java

Codecademy In progress

HTML/CSS Codecademy 2016

Philosophy UC Santa Barbara 2014-2015

**IGETC** 

Irvine Valley College 2011-2014

## **INTERESTS**

Cycling

Hiking

Reading

## 

Bug Reporting

Troubleshooting

HTML & CSS

Java